Location: TN Change [View State Page](https://www.ducks.org/ "View State Page")

    How We Conserve
    
    Read more about how DU helps conservation efforts
    
    Our Initiatives
    
    Connecting people and resources with crucial habitats
    
    More Conservation
    
    Explore everything DU and Conservation!
    
    * [Landowners Find out about collaboration with private landowners](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/conserving-wetlands-waterfowl#landowners)
    * [Acquiring Land Learn about strategic land acquisition for habitat](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/conserving-wetlands-waterfowl#land)
    * [Find DU Projects Near You
        
        Explore conservation efforts in your area!](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/where-ducks-unlimited-works#find-projects "Find DU Projects Near You")
    
    * [Boreal Forest Explore efforts in the vast North American Boreal Forest](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/boreal-forest-initiative)
    * [Great Lakes Learn about habitat protection in the Great Lakes](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/great-lakes-initiative)
    * [Living Lakes See how MN and IA's lakes support migrating waterfowl](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/living-lakes-initiative)
    * [Preserve our Prairies Understand efforts to protect crucial waterfowl habitats](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/preserve-our-prairies-initiative)
    * [America's River Explore Mississippi River's waterfowl habitat restoration](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/americas-river-initiative)
    * [Big Rivers Discover the restoration of Mississippi River habitats](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/big-rivers-initiative)
    * [California Wetlands Learn about revitalizing California's wetlands](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/california-wetlands-initiative)
    * [Completing the Cycle Understand Atlantic Flyway habitat sustainability](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/completing-the-cycle-initiative)
    * [See All
        
        Discover all of our conservation initiatives](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives)
    
    * [Conservation Home Protecting, enhancing, restoring America's wetlands](https://www.ducks.org/conservation)
    * [National Stories Conservation updates from across the country](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/national)
    * [Waterfowl Research Explore waterfowl science and research findings](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/waterfowl-research-science)
    * [Find DU Projects Near You Explore conservation efforts in your area!](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/where-ducks-unlimited-works)
    * [Sustainability Focusing on wetland sustainability and biodiversity](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/sustainability)
    * [Make a Difference Join, volunteer, and support wetland conservation](https://www.ducks.org/get-involved)

    * [
        
        DU Expedition Shirt
        
        Join today](https://donate.ducks.org/donateonlinesecure.aspx?promokey=expeditionshirtjoin&ID=14301&responsecode=CQH0AAAA&or=1)

    * [Newsroom Read press releases, articles & more on DU's conservation efforts](https://www.ducks.org/newsroom)
    * [Watch & Listen Explore DU's video and podcast library: there's something for everyone!](https://www.ducks.org/media/du-podcast)
    * [DU Magazine Expert tips, stunning photography, & more: Subscribe to DU magazine today](https://www.ducks.org/media/du-magazine)
    * [Photo Gallery Experience wildlife in action through DU's photo gallery](https://www.ducks.org/media/photo-gallery)
    * [E-Newsletter Get the latest news and updates from DU delivered straight to you](https://www.ducks.org/newsletter)
    * [Mobile App Access exclusive features, tips, & more by downloading DU's app](https://www.ducks.org/media/mobile-app)
    * [
        
        DU Expedition Shirt
        
        Join today](https://donate.ducks.org/donateonlinesecure.aspx?promokey=expeditionshirtjoin&ID=14301&responsecode=CQH0AAAA&or=1)

Your Location

Change [View State Page](https://www.ducks.org/)

* How We Conserve
    
    * [Landowners Find out about collaboration with private landowners](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/conserving-wetlands-waterfowl#landowners)
    * [Acquiring Land Learn about strategic land acquisition for habitat](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/conserving-wetlands-waterfowl#land)
    * [Find DU Projects Near You
        
        Explore conservation efforts in your area!](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/where-ducks-unlimited-works#find-projects "Find DU Projects Near You")
    
* Our Initiatives
    
    * [Boreal Forest Explore efforts in the vast North American Boreal Forest](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/boreal-forest-initiative)
    * [Great Lakes Learn about habitat protection in the Great Lakes](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/great-lakes-initiative)
    * [Living Lakes See how MN and IA's lakes support migrating waterfowl](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/living-lakes-initiative)
    * [Preserve our Prairies Understand efforts to protect crucial waterfowl habitats](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/preserve-our-prairies-initiative)
    * [America's River Explore Mississippi River's waterfowl habitat restoration](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/americas-river-initiative)
    * [Big Rivers Discover the restoration of Mississippi River habitats](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/big-rivers-initiative)
    * [California Wetlands Learn about revitalizing California's wetlands](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/california-wetlands-initiative)
    * [Completing the Cycle Understand Atlantic Flyway habitat sustainability](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives/completing-the-cycle-initiative)
    * [See All
        
        Discover all of our conservation initiatives](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/du-conservation-initiatives)
    
* More Conservation
    * [Conservation Home Protecting, enhancing, restoring America's wetlands](https://www.ducks.org/conservation)
    * [National Stories Conservation updates from across the country](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/national)
    * [Waterfowl Research Explore waterfowl science and research findings](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/waterfowl-research-science)
    * [Find DU Projects Near You Explore conservation efforts in your area!](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/where-ducks-unlimited-works)
    * [Sustainability Focusing on wetland sustainability and biodiversity](https://www.ducks.org/conservation/sustainability)
    * [Make a Difference Join, volunteer, and support wetland conservation](https://www.ducks.org/get-involved)

* [
    
    DU Expedition Shirt
    
    Join today](https://donate.ducks.org/donateonlinesecure.aspx?promokey=expeditionshirtjoin&ID=14301&responsecode=CQH0AAAA&or=1)

* [Newsroom Read press releases, articles & more on DU's conservation efforts](https://www.ducks.org/newsroom)
* [Watch & Listen Explore DU's video and podcast library: there's something for everyone!](https://www.ducks.org/media/du-podcast)
* [DU Magazine Expert tips, stunning photography, & more: Subscribe to DU magazine today](https://www.ducks.org/media/du-magazine)
* [Photo Gallery Experience wildlife in action through DU's photo gallery](https://www.ducks.org/media/photo-gallery)
* [E-Newsletter Get the latest news and updates from DU delivered straight to you](https://www.ducks.org/newsletter)
* [Mobile App Access exclusive features, tips, & more by downloading DU's app](https://www.ducks.org/media/mobile-app)
* [
    
    DU Expedition Shirt
    
    Join today](https://donate.ducks.org/donateonlinesecure.aspx?promokey=expeditionshirtjoin&ID=14301&responsecode=CQH0AAAA&or=1)

Privacy Policy
==============

_Updated June 1, 2021_

It is important for you to know the Privacy Policy (the "Policy") of Ducks Unlimited, Inc. ("DU") before interacting with DU, including using any feature of [www.ducks.org](https://www.ducks.org/) or any of its affiliated sites, apps and platforms including social media (collectively, the "Web Site"). DU takes your privacy seriously and wants you to know what information is being collected and how it may be used, stored and shared by DU. By using the Web Site or otherwise providing Personal Information (defined below), you indicate your consent to the collection and use of information as outlined in the Policy. Please take a few minutes to read this Policy.

The Policy does not cover information collected on outside websites linked to the Web Site. You should carefully check each website to learn its privacy policy because that website's policy may significantly differ from DU's Policy. DU is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of other websites you may visit.

**1\. Collection and use of personal information**

DU collects information that may be used to identify an individual ("Personal Information") from individuals who use the Web Site, including but not limited to the following information:

The user's name, address, phone number and e-mail address; the user's DU membership number; tracking information about which pages users access and utilize; information volunteered by the user, such as survey information; social media profile information, including pictures and IDs. 

If you provide credit card information to DU, the credit card information will only be used for the purpose for which it was provided. DU does not store credit card information.

DU collects Personal Information over the Web Sites, but also over the phone, in email, through face-to-face conversation, via mail, chat forums, surveys, donation forms, and registration at events. DU also contracts with third parties to provide information on individuals that may be interested in information about DU, including our conservation work and potential donors. 

If you do not provide the Personal Information, DU may be unable to provide you with personal and optimized digital experience you desire out of DU. If you disclose Personal Information to DU about other individuals, you represent that you have the authority to do so. 

DU uses the Personal Information to conduct legitimate business functions, including providing you with relevant content that you may be interested in. That may include information on our conservation services, membership information, promotions, invitations to events, donor information, and general business information. DU may also use your Personal Information to respond to questions from you, manage DU's own business and otherwise comply with legal obligations. 

DU will also use the Personal Information to provide specialized and personalized content that DU thinks you might be interested in. Sometimes, our promotions, sweepstakes or other promotions have specific rules. Please read those rules carefully. 

DU may also use the Personal Information to respond to requests from government authorities, law enforcement or for other legal reasons. 

If you would like DU to not share your Personal Information with third parties for the purpose of renting or exchanging its mailing list, if you would like to opt-out of receiving mail from DU, or if you would like to opt out of telemarketing, you may call 901-758-3825 or email [privacy@ducks.org](mailto:privacy@ducks.org). 

DU maintains a list of donors, members, and former members only. Personal information on non-members solicited by DU is not maintained in DU's database. If you are a non-member and would like your information removed from a mailing list, there are numerous resources online. One recommended resource is: [https://dmachoice.thedma.org](https://dmachoice.thedma.org/)

DU (or its service providers) may use the information we collect (for instance, IP addresses and unique mobile device identifiers) to locate or try to locate the same unique users across multiple browsers or devices (such as smartphones, tablets, or computers), or work with providers that do this, in order to better tailor content and features and provide you with a seamless experience across devices. If you wish to opt out of cross-device tracking for purposes of interest-based advertising, you may do so through your device settings. We may also use cross-device targeting to help identify our users and service advertising. This type of advertising is often called "interest-based" or "personalized" advertising – and when it occurs on mobile apps, "cross-app" advertising. 

You can learn more about interest-based advertising and how to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising by visiting (1) the Network Advertising Initiative's Consumer Opt-out link ([http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1)) or (2) the Digital Advertising Alliance's Consumer Opt-out link ([http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)). To opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising or customize Google display network ads, you can visit the Google Ads Setting Page. Please note that, even if you opt-out, you may still receive advertisements from us. However, in that case, the advertising will not be tailored to your interests. Also, DU does not control any of the above opt-out links or whether any particular company chooses to participate in these opt-out programs.

If you would like to opt-out of receiving e-mails, you should use the "unsubscribe" feature at the bottom of all DU emails.

If you would like to access, modify or delete your Personal Information, you may do so to the extent this right is provided by law. Please contact us at 901-758-3825 or email [privacy@ducks.org](mailto:privacy@ducks.org) to make such a request. We may need to verify your identify before providing access to, modifying or deleting any Personal Information. If you request deletion, DU will keep Personal Information until any transactions currently in process are complete, and then only to the extent necessary to implement your request. 

**2\. Children may not divulge personally identifiable information**

No Personal Information should be submitted to the Web Site by users under 13 years of age. On this Web Site, DU does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from users under 13 years of age.

**3\. Our use of "cookies" and other information**

DU may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a Web Site user's computer. Cookies are nuggets of information that are placed by a web site in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to track usage patterns on the Web Site, to record registration and personalization information, and to assist you with navigation of the Web Site. Cookies also help DU determine which advertisements you might be most interested in. Other sites linked to the Web Site may use cookies in different ways; again, you should consult the privacy policy of each website you visit.

If you do not want information collected through cookies, most browsers have a simple mechanism to disable the use of cookies. If you do not use cookies on the Web Site, your experience may vary.

Additionally, DU may collect other information that does not qualify as Personal Information. For example, DU may collect information about the type of computer or device you are using, your location, browser type and language using Google Analytics and other services. This type of information is often collected automatically by webpages you visit to help calculate usage levels and determine what content is most interesting. This information may also be used to diagnose problems and administer the services DU provides. 

**4\. Sharing information**

DU reserves the right to use, distribute, sell, rent and share all of the information it gathers through the Web Site, including Personal Information, for any and all purposes. Without limiting the foregoing, DU routinely uses the information for its own marketing, promotional and membership activities; DU also shares the information with its corporate partners and with interested third parties, who may use the information for their own sales, marketing and promotional activities, and who may have privacy policies that differ from DU's. However, DU does not share member e-mail addresses or Mobile Opt.

DU will provide Personal Information about you in response to a subpoena, a statute, a court order or a valid legal process. In addition, DU may reveal Personal Information about you to a third person in order to protect the personal safety of DU's members, employees or the public.

**5\. Modifications to the privacy policy**

At its sole discretion, DU may change its Policy, with or without prior notice to you. When DU does make changes, DU will post those changes on the Web Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web Site. Please check the Policy from time to time so that you may be aware of any changes.

**6\. Location Services**

Location Services allows the Web Site to gather and use information based on the current location of your mobile device to provide a variety of location-based services. For example, the Web Site might use your location data to provide local weather information, assist hunting-related tools, inform you of local events, etc., based on your current location.

By enabling Location Services for your devices, you agree and consent to the transmission, collection, maintenance, processing, and use of your location data and location search queries by the Web Site and its partners and licensees to provide location-based products and services.

**7\. Disputes**

Any disputes regarding this Policy, as well as any disputes arising from your use of this Web Site, shall be governed by the laws of the State of Tennessee, without giving effect to the conflicts of laws provisions thereof. By using the Web Site you irrevocably agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Shelby County Circuit Court or the United States District Court for the Western District of Tennessee at Memphis in connection with any suit, action or other proceeding concerning the Policy and/or your use of the Web Site.

**8\. Data Security**

DU believes securing your Personal Information is important. DU uses industry-standard controls, technologies, and on-line security techniques to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access. All credit card information provided to Ducks Unlimited is transmitted using Norton Secure (Verisign) SSL encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to DU. Additionally, Ducks Unlimited complies with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) for all credit card information submitted on the Web Site. DU utilizes a third-party processor for payments, and that processor may have your Personal Information that is not subject to this Policy. Ducks Unlimited does not store your credit card information on a permanent basis. Unfortunately, while DU makes every effort to ensure your Personal Information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While DU strives to protect your Personal Information, DU cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.

OTHER WEB SITES:

Our Web Site contains links to other unrelated websites. Please note when you click on one of these links you are entering another website for which Ducks Unlimited has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.

**9\. Questions?**

The Web Site is maintained by Ducks Unlimited, Inc., One Waterfowl Way, Memphis, Tennessee, U.S., 38120. If you have questions regarding DU or this policy, or if you would like your personal information excluded from information shared per No. 4 above, please contact us at 901-758-3825.

* ##### DU Magazine
    
    Features for avid sportsmen and women, equipment profiles, buyer's guides, natural history stories, photographic essays, and more.

* ##### DU Online Store
    
    Official DU merchandise, clothing, hunting gear, gifts & more

* ##### DU App
    
    The official DU App is the ultimate resource for waterfowl hunters! Access the DU Migration Map, Waterfowler’s Journal, Waterfowl ID, DU events and more. The DU App includes tools that are important to DU supporters, waterfowlers, and conservationists throughout North America.
    
* ##### DU Podcast
    
    Learn more about ducks, geese, wetlands conservation efforts, and all things waterfowl hunting.

* ##### DU TV
    
    The latest season of Ducks Unlimited TV brings you more of the best waterfowling action, tips and tactics, and conservation news. DU TV airs July through December on the Sportsman Channel.

* ##### Careers at Ducks Unlimited
    
    Looking for a great place to work? Check out our job listings and start working for Team DU!

* ##### Follow DU
    
    * [](https://twitter.com/DucksUnlimited "Ducks Unlimited X (formerly Twitter)")

© 2024 Ducks Unlimited.

Select Location

X

State Abbreviation or Zip

 Go

Use Current Location

X

No Yes

X

X

Share this photo
